Alaska, Oregon and Washington State
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Alaska, Oregon and Washington State
2.1.2.4.9.1
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1380
- Alaska, Oregon and Washington State, 2.1.2.4.9.1
  - Group of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Group of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Group of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Group of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Group of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Group of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Camp of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Camp of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Camp of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Camp of people native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Children native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Children native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Woman and boy native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Man and girl native to Alaska[?], circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Kayaker, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Panorama of town, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Panorama of town, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Snowscape, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Snowscape, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Water scenery, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Water scenery, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Water scenery, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Water scenery, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Water scenery, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Water scenery, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Water scenery, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  - Barren trees, circa 1900-1920; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1380)
  Box 1381
- Alaska, Oregon and Washington State, 2.1.2.4.9.1
  - Men unloading boat, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Ship (Alaska) in port, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Ship (Ohio) in port, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Ships in port, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Ships in port, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Ship at sea, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Ship at sea, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - View from ship, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - View from ship, mountain panorama, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Boats docked, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Saloon, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Industrial building, circa 1900-1920; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Industrial camp, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - People in garden, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Cabin, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Cabin, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Cabin, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Cabin, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - House, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - House, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - House, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Houses, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Tent, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Fishermen, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Unloading salmon at cannery, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Fishermen, circa 1900-1920; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Cannery, circa 1900-1920; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Cannery, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Prospector, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Man operating hydraulic monitor, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Mountain climbers, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Men on trail, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Men on trail, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Man on deck of ship, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Loggers, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Men and horses crossing stream, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  - Dog sled, circa 1900-1920; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1381)
  Box 1382
- Alaska, Oregon and Washington State, 2.1.2.4.9.1
  - Group of women by waterside, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - People posing atop hill, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Two men, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Men standing in front of Wells Fargo and Co. Express Office, sign reads, “Umalilla will go to Seattle via Cordova and Miles Glacier”, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Two men and woman pose before storefront, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Two men and woman, bear rolling on ground, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Woman posing in front of Tolovana building, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - People in railroad car, circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - White Pass and Yukon railroad car, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Damaged railroad bridge, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Bridge, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Men and automobile, circa 1900-1920; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Men and woman in automobile, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Automobile on bridge, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Three men in automobile, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Automobile on road, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Automobile, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Person standing behind automobile, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Women standing in front of automobile, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Automobiles, circa 1900-1920; 20; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Boat on water near shore, circa 1900-1920; 21; 3x4 color (Box 1382)
  - Man on dock, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1382)